Okay, then I'll share my screen, I'll just...
Okay, so I'm just sharing my screen as that came up for everyone?
Yeah, perfect.
Add just a few more people joining now.
Okay, let's get started.
So today's call is Up Your Game with G.
So, we thought that we would do a call on navigating the new version of "Add At
Work"
because I feel like some people are getting a lot of bit confused with some
things as things have changed now
and it's just good to have a call on this because obviously this is the site
that we're using all the time
so we want to make sure we feel confident in operating it.
So I'm going to go through that today.
Okay, so "Add At Work" is our host platform and it's useful to get to know how
to make the most of it
as it is your business at the end of the day.
The info we will chat about today is the best of our knowledge
but as the platform's changing and updating a lot, it's always best to just
check with your mentor
if anything that we say now in the future doesn't make sense, it might mean
something's been changed
but yeah, this is how it operates at the moment.
So I'm going to log in to my profile and just go through some things on the new
site
just to show how to navigate it all.
Okay.
So for me, whenever I open "Add At Work" it always opens the older version.
So I'll just log into that and then I'll show you how to switch to the new one
and then we can go through the new version together.
Okay, so I'm just going to go and broadcast now.
Yeah, in Dashboard, it should take you to the new site.
Yeah, perfect. Okay.
So I'll have both open actually and I'll flip between the both to show you this
in the contrast.
And the difference, so this is the older version and this is the newer version.
To be honest, I'm not sure what my preference is yet because I'm still kind of
attached to the old one
as I've known that this whole time, but I do think that this newer one is
probably a little bit better
regarding presentation and how it all looks and stuff like that.
So we just learn how to use this properly.
Should be good.
So as you can see along here, we have all different options of different parts
of the website to explore.
But then up here in the top right hand corner, this is also something you can
click on
to bring up more features of the website.
Now on the older version, yeah, it's just all along the top.
As you can see, how to navigate the site is all here.
There's nothing up in this top corner.
So that's a little bit different there.
But overall, you know, it's quite similar regarding what you can do.
Of course, you know, what features the site has.
It's all the same stuff, but just it just looks a little bit different and laid
out a little bit differently.
So I'll just go through a little bit of it now.
So this is the home page.
Yeah, you can see in everyone who's online, check out some movies, galleries,
live chat and whatnot.
Pretty similar to the home page here.
But instead to go through the different options, you'd click on here, webcam,
and then you'd see everyone online.
Now up here in the top right hand corner, this is a lot of stuff to do with
your profile, your credits.
This is basically about going online and all stuff like that.
So if there's anything regarding your profile, it's going to be up here in the
top right hand corner.
And then these tabs along here are more through navigating the site.
So let's go through some of this here.
So as you can see on this be here, you've got my profile, security, direct cam,
your hot lists.
There's a lot of different things you can do here.
I'll just show you how to live stream as this is the most important.
This is what we're all here for us to go online.
So you want to click here on my direct cam.
And then this actually opens up the dashboard for setting your availability,
your position and special offers and your direct cam settings.
So in here, you can edit a lot regarding your cam settings, also your category
and strap line.
And if you wanted to link your Twitter, you do all that here.
And then to go live, we can just click here on start direct cam.
And then it should pop up with a new window with your page to go online.
Obviously here you can press start to start the stream, I'm not going to stream
now.
But this page actually, it's really good.
I like what they've done here because although you do have all of the features
on the main site to be able to edit things with your profile and stuff like
that,
you can actually just do it from this page, which is a lot easier.
So if you click up here in the top right hand corner on these three dots and
click settings, you can edit a lot in here, which is great.
It just saves time if I'm going back to this site and back to this page, you
can just do it all here.
So you can turn your free mode on and off, which is very convenient when you're
on cam.
And you do have to log out quickly.
So if I was already pressed start, somebody else is joining, sorry, one moment.
If I was already to press start, I wouldn't be able to edit it. I'll just press
start and show you actually.
Show you what I mean.
So now it's kind of to me to come.
And if I was to go here on settings, I'll just let it load first one moment.
Okay. So now I'm live. So if I was to pin off my free mode and save changes, it
will log me off.
Because you need to be loved out when you're making any changes to your cam, to
your free mode or whatever else.
So now it's just automatically restarted and logged me back in.
So now I'll be on free mode. So I'm going to log out straight away because I
don't want to be on free mode.
So yeah, in here you can enable your free mode. You can change your price per
minute.
You can check what camera is used. You know, maybe you've got a plug-in camera
that you use instead of your main one.
That's where you'll change there.
Again, with the microphone, you can change the font size of the chat box, the
sounds and other options.
So yeah, I think this is a really great tool right on the cam screen.
And again, they've got something else in here, which is also great that we use
all the time.
They've got the boost button. So if you press this, you can bid a certain
amount of credits to be on the front page for the next hour.
So it's good and handy that it's all in one place.
Okay, I'll come on to that.
And there's just one more thing I wanted to show you on the new site.
So usually on the old site, on the old version, you'd go here to go to your
emails.
On the new one, it's just a mail thing there. You just click on that and it
opens your emails.
But yeah, I think that's all for the new site.
There's obviously a lot I could sit here and go through and it would take up
the whole hour of the call.
So I won't do that. But we do actually have a video on the members area of the
website and I go through everything.
So if there's something you're not really sure about how to use on the new site
, you can look at that video.
But yeah, I just wanted to go through a couple of things today.
And if you do prefer the old one and you prefer to just switch back to the old
one, that's also okay.
I'll show you how to do that now. There'll be a few ways of doing it, but this
is how I do it.
So I go to my profile, edit profile and then it takes me back to the old site.
And then you can just press home again and there you are back on the old site.
Okay, so I think that's enough for that for now.
Just want to make sure that everyone's back on the same screen.
Okay, everyone can see my power points.
Yeah.
What are we looking for?
I'm just checking that you're able to see my power points that is on now.
That's back to the main screen.
Well, you're getting with Jane now they're getting the new version of it.
Okay.
Thank you. I just wanted to make sure you guys could see that.
So we've been through and had a look at the new version of as it work.
But yeah, just have a little play around with it.
It is once you've, you know, had a little sauce on it and locked through it.
It's not that difficult, but it's, like I said, it is basically the same thing
that you're doing just presented in a different way.
Okay. So now we're going to go through fixing account problems.
So sometimes there are issues on AdultWork with your profile.
So I'll have a little chat about what you might face and how to deal with that.
So as we know, there can be issues on AdultWork.
So I'll go through some common problems you may face to know how to fix them.
Of course, you can always ask your mentor for help, but maybe they aren't
available right away.
So at least this way, you can fix the problem yourself and get back online
without having to wait for your mentor to respond.
Because yeah, you know, sometimes maybe something's happened and you can just
fix it yourself right away without having to wait, which will be a little bit
more convenient for you.
But of course, if it's something that you kind of fix or you'd rather just wait
for them to do it, that's also fine.
Okay.
So this is a big one. This probably has happened to most people if you've been
away from camp for a little while.
So if you don't go on camp for a couple of weeks to a month, they will switch
off your webcam services.
This happened to one of our girls recently, actually, and I mean, it happens.
It happens all the time, actually, but it's very simple to get them put back on
.
So I'll show you how to do it and you don't have to wait for us to do it.
I'm going to log on and say, oh, and my webcam service off. I'm ready to go
online.
You know, I've done my hair to make up, got my outfit on, and now I can't go on
.
Instead of waiting for it to be fixed, you can probably just fix it yourself
and get yourself online.
So I'll show how to do that now.
So logged into my profile. So on my details, click registration details.
And then here, you simply just tick this box. So if you were, obviously, if
they've been turned off, it'll be on ticked like this.
Simply just tick it and press save.
And then you're back online. You're back ready to come again.
Now, there will be some profiles that you'll have a message up here that says
you're not able to do this yourself.
So that would mean you'd have to contact your mentor and then we will write an
AdultWork and ask them to turn them back on.
This is for profiles who've maybe been inactive for a very, very long time.
So if you've not been online for a while, this is probably what you'll have to
do.
But if you're someone who's going on criteria regularly and it's just been a
couple of weeks or even a couple of months, it's likely you can turn them back
on yourself.
And so that's how that's done.
Just notice a question in the chat box. Let's see.
So you know the phone chat one below that.
Yeah, if I click on that, does that put phone chat on as well?
Yeah, exactly that. So which whichever ones you click, it will turn on.
I think content creator is normally just ticked for everyone, but we can all
keep that ticked because we all have content on our profile.
But yeah, phone chat, SMS, escort, alternative, whatever it is, you just press
tick and save and then that will turn it on.
All right.
Okay, let's go through the next problem that you might face.
Okay, so maybe it's been a really long time that you've been online and your
account has been deactivated.
So it'll come up where that your account's been deactivated when you try login
and then there'll be a reactivate me button.
So you can click that and go through the steps or you can contact the help desk
or contact your mentor as well.
That's absolutely fine.
I'm going to show you how to contact the help desk in just a moment.
I'll go through the next steps first and then I'll show you how to do that
because contacting the help desk, it's actually good for any issue.
So if there are any problems at all in your profile or even if you just want to
ask a question or, you know, gain more insight into something, you can just ask
the help desk.
And to be honest, they are quite good.
They respond usually within 24 to 48 hours.
And then it's just like a message thread so you can just ask them more
questions in there.
Okay, so if you are unable to login or the website freezes, usually it's just
fixed by restarting your device.
So just restart your laptop or phone, whatever it is you're using, and then you
should be able to just login as normal.
If you try to login in, let's say your username and password is not recognised,
just ask your mentor to change your password.
I don't know what this is, why this happens.
It must be some sort of glitch, but a few times over the years I've seen this
as to where the usual username and password isn't working.
What we can log into your profile through the group page so we can get into it
another way, and then we can change your password and then it just logs you in
fine.
But yeah, even if it has a mean change, I don't know why sometimes it doesn't,
it's not recognised, but this is just a simple way to fix it.
Chloe, are you okay to explain this one about the timeout message?
Are you there?
Thank you.
Do you hear me? I'm hearing you okay?
Yes.
Yeah, so I get this quite a lot because I'm really bad at walking away.
We've got a bad habit of walking away from me that's off while I'm working.
And I'm sure everyone knows that some clients will literally only bring you for
three seconds, and if you don't answer in that three seconds, it'll hang up.
If that happens a couple of times, I've noticed it can be anywhere between
missing two calls to about six, and it doesn't have to be in a row either.
You can miss one call and then have a call and then miss another one and you
can still send the same message.
The log you know completely and a big red message will come up and it'll just
say this is for paying clients, you're missing too many calls, you're now in a
timeout for 15 minutes.
It looks scarier than it is. I've had this message loads of times, you're not
going to get in any further trouble.
They're not going to suspend you, they're not going to take you to count or
anything.
It literally happens to me about 15 times at this point.
It does look quite frightening, because it's this big red thing, and if you do
try and log back on, it'll just say no, it won't let you log back on, so you do
have to waste the full 15 minutes.
But then once the 15 minutes is over there, you can then log back in as normal
and then just try and not miss any calls.
It's just because we get to spot checks a lot as well.
So I think it's luck of the draw, whether you might be getting a spot check at
that time and stuff as well.
Well, it looks scarier than it is, and it's easy to leave as well to do stuff
so it's the 15 minutes.
If I thank you, Chloe.
Yeah, I've never actually had that one yet, to be honest, I said, yeah, because
I'm sure that I will at some point.
But yeah, like I said, maybe it just looks scarier than it is, so yeah, I don't
worry too much about that one.
Thank you.
Okay.
Okay, so if your text messages aren't working, you might need to contact your
network provider and ask for premium numbers to be added onto your package.
So this is for the ladies who do SMS, and maybe, you know, it's just not when
you're trying to connect your phone to add a work.
It's just not working.
It might be because your contract or whatever it is, it's not allowing for this
extra service for the premium numbers.
So just call them up, like vote a phone, whoever it is, and ask for the premium
numbers to be added, and that should fix that problem.
So for the ladies who do phone calls, your phone call availability is turned
off every two hours.
So you need to turn it back on yourself every two hours that you want to be,
you know, showing that you're available to receive phone calls.
AdultWork will text you and say, you need to text a code to add a work to get
your number 10 back on, or to get your availability 10 back on, I should say.
But you don't need to do this.
You can just turn it on via the website.
So how you do this is you go to phone call availability on my details, click
your availability available now, and then click I'm available for phone chat
bookings.
And you know, that's going to turn that on for the next two hours, and then
every two hours you just need to keep turning it back on again.
And finally, oh, there's two more, sorry.
So if AdultWork isn't loading, that might mean that there is an adult content
blocker enabled.
So basically whatever Wi-Fi you're using, it doesn't allow you to go onto over
18 sites.
So it's not a problem with AdultWork or whatever, it's the Wi-Fi that you're
using in that moment.
So what you'd have to do then is you'd have to call your Wi-Fi provider and ask
them to turn off this feature.
So to just allow you to access what other site you want, we have seen this
quite a lot over the years as well as issue.
And finally, any other issues at all, contact the helpdesk or of course your
mentor.
So I will show you how to contact the helpdesk now, which actually can be a
really good feature actually.
So to contact the helpdesk, we want to go back to AdultWork.com and then log in
and click help.
And then it'll come up with this screen here, it'll come up with all different,
like, FAQs.
So you can have a look at the different questions, maybe it's already answered
there.
But if you're what you want to find out doesn't seem to be answered on the site
, you can just sign in to this helpdesk.
And then up here, click contact us.
Now you're just going to submit a request here.
So you can just choose default ticker form, so that means you can speak about
anything in this form.
Or you can go through and see if your exact issue is there.
So for example, I think towards the bottom, it's got something about the
activation or something like that.
But you have a verification request and stuff like that.
Yeah, so you can choose one of those or you can just choose default ticker form
.
You put your username, the second and last character of your password.
And then here you can tick which issue describes your which one describes your
issue the most.
If you can't see it in there, just click over.
You write the subject, so I don't know, my webcam services are being turned off
.
You could write, for example, and then write a description, you can say, "Hey,
my webcam services are being turned off.
You can't allow me to turn them back on myself. Can you please put them back on
? I want to go online ASAP."
Something along those lines.
If you need to attach a file, a photo or a screen chart to show them what's
going on, you can do that here.
And then you can press submit.
And then to check on how your form is doing when they responded, you click up
here in the top right hand corner and click my activities.
And then it will come up with all of the different forms you've sent off, all
of the questions you've asked over the years and the answers, I'll just click
into this one to show you.
So this was what I asked them and then they responded here and we had a little
chat back and forth.
So yeah, the help desk can be a good feature with fixing issues.
Okay, let's go back to the PowerPoint.
Here we go.
Okay.
Does anyone have any questions at this moment by the way, or am I going too
fast?
Yes, I have got a question.
Sure, go ahead.
I have asked, but I just want to verify November the third I'm going to New
Zealand for three weeks.
And I would like to do coming from there. Is there anything I need to do or is,
you know, so that I can continue there.
Do I need to take my own Wi-Fi or can I log it in through somebody else's Wi-Fi
.
To be honest, if you're going to go on holiday, I would definitely recommend
just letting the help desk know that you're going to be away.
Usually they don't, like it doesn't matter, you can come anywhere in the world
or most places in the world, I should say.
Yeah.
But I think it's worth just letting them know to say, hey, I'm going to be in
New Zealand on these dates.
I'm likely to come on some of these, like while I'm there, just so they know.
Because if they think they see you logged in from England and then all of a
sudden logged in from somewhere else,
maybe they think, oh, someone else logged into a profile or something like that
.
So just avoid that happen and you can let the help desk know.
And regarding the Wi-Fi issue, like if you could take your own Wi-Fi, as I
mentioned before, some Wi-Fi's do have an adult content blocker on.
Yeah.
But it's not that common.
Most Wi-Fi's don't have it.
So it's up to you if you're able to bring your own Wi-Fi and bring away of
connecting yourself, then pay a fax because then you'll know you won't have any
issues.
Yeah.
So yeah, is that possible? Are you able to take like a Wi-Fi box or something
like that?
Mine's called a MIFI. It's just a small thing.
Because I'm in the motorhome, aren't I? So I can take it everywhere.
Ah, okay. That's perfect then. I suppose you may as well take that just in case
they did have an adult blocker. Yeah, they did.
From an Airbnb or hotel, you're probably not likely to be able to call the Wi-
Fi provider because it's not obviously in your name.
So yeah, bring in your own Wi-Fi will definitely cut off that problem, for sure
.
Okay. Yeah.
Yes, you can either let the help desk know yourself or let your mentor know the
exact date you're going to be away.
And we can tell work that you want to be aware, just so if you do log in that
they recognise that it's you and not somebody else kind of thing.
Okay. That's great. Okay. Perfect.
Sorry, just going to go back to the PowerPoint.
Okay.
Now, let's take a look at some profile maintenance.
We've got the lovely Chloe's profile here.
This is really good actually. You've got almost everything that speak of us. I
think you've got on here.
So your profile is the very first thing that your clients will see before they
even see you.
So making sure it's the very best it can be is important.
We recommend updating your profile regularly and below are some suggestions for
your profile.
Wishlist. So you can add a wishlist to your profile, even if, you know, not
many people buy new things on here.
It's still, I think it looks good just to bulk your profile out more, just to
have more on there.
And as you can see, Chloe's got one on hers here.
And you can add this on quite easily. You go to a tab called more and then you
can browse through all the items on our work and add them to your wishlist.
You can only add items that are on our work site as in, you know, you can't
search for something on a random website and add it into the wishlist.
There's only a specific amount of items that you can add in there.
But there are some, you know, good things you can add in there and could be a
bonus that people actually end up buying you all of these things.
So probably we're spending like 10 minutes or so adding stuff on there and then
it's on there for life.
And hopefully you'll get gifted one day.
So you can add content to sales. You can add pictures and videos and also
custom content to your profile.
So now that the rules have changed and the front of the profile needs to be a
little bit more PG.
I think it actually works out well for our private galleries because the only
way the customers can see explicit photos is to pay.
Whereas in the past, you were allowed to have more revealing profile and more
revealing photos in your main profile in the free bit.
But now they all have to pay to see that. So that's good.
So you can make a private gallery, as I'm sure a lot of you already know.
You can charge whatever you want for this.
Put as many pictures as you want in there.
The more pictures, the more you can charge.
And yeah, you can upload videos.
So for the videos, it's a bit different.
Each video has its own price.
And you can also do custom content.
So you can actually upload videos and albums of photos.
And with a specific code, which is only for certain clients.
So for example, you might have a foot fetish client and they might say,
"I want to buy a photo of your feet or I want to buy a video of your feet."
And you might not want to put that on your main profile for everyone else to be
able to purchase.
You might only want certain clients to be able to view that.
So then you can create a folder just for these specific clients with foot
fetish and who have foot fetish.
And then you can tell them how to access this.
Of course, they have to pay as well.
And if you're doing custom content, you can actually charge a little bit more.
Because it's not just on there being sold to the masses, constantly making
money off the same thing.
This is something specific for one person.
So you can charge more for this.
You can discuss with them how much that it's going to be in the private chat or
in the emails.
But yeah, I think this is a good feature to use.
Can I ask, please, what's an average of what you can charge for a photo or a
video?
Just average.
OK, I think it depends on what you're doing in the photo or video.
So yeah, what type of photo or video are you talking about?
Well, say a foot fetish, for instance, what would you charge for?
If I was going to sell a photo album of maybe 10 photos with foot fetish,
you could probably charge around 30 to 50 credits for this.
This is what I would charge the fingers as well.
You know, people have different ways of doing it.
I know some girls who charge less and sell more, so then they end up making a
lot.
Whereas others, they prefer to not sell as many, not put the content out there
for everyone,
but charge more for it.
So it just depends how you like to do it.
There's no right or wrong answer here.
And what about the content?
I mean, are you, I know that AdultWork are becoming a bit work?
So, for instance, could you have any explicit photos in a private gallery?
Yeah, you can.
This is why this new rule actually does work in our favour because you can't
have explicit
ones on your free party or profile.
You can have them in the private gallery.
So the clients probably going to see your main pictures and think, Oh, I wish I
could see more
of here.
And then they know they can the private gallery where it's in the past.
They could have just viewed it in your free gallery for free if you did have
ones like
that in there.
But now they do have to pay to see that kind of stuff.
So I think that's, that's good.
And what's a no, no, what's a no, no, what you can't do now.
You can't have on your main, like on your main profile photos.
I know on the main profile in private, what's known knows in private.
In private.
Yeah.
Actually, jeez, daddy.
You can't have any children's toys in any pictures, including your private.
So I know that sounds a bit strange.
But even if you've got a teddy bear in the background, they'll take that down.
I had a few pictures that night from a shoes and I was holding a teddy bear.
And they were just like, no, absolutely not.
Or even if it's like a picture or no photos in the background, even if it's not
of anyone
or even if it's a view, these don't like pictures or toys or anything like that
.
Obviously, not sex or use book.
Like things like a teddy bear or anything.
They don't like that.
They'll just take that.
So if you, if you did a, you know, a live video to sell.
Of say you're an eating.
Can you do that?
I think so.
But to be honest, you can always just write to the help desk.
Hey, I'm thinking about uploading a video to my private gallery.
Or, you know, like, you know, make sure they know it's not on the main thing of
me.
You're an eating or whatever it is.
Is that, is that, is that going to be accepted?
Maybe you can ask them first.
If you think that it might be something on the border of what's going to be
okay or not,
it might be worth just double checking.
If you do videos, so just no music in the background and as well.
Yeah, because they'll take that down as well.
I'll be ready.
Yes.
But I think I've definitely seen girls have videos of both sports.
That's what it is.
Isn't it on there?
But I don't remember seeing anything since the rules have changed.
But because it's a paid for, like, video, I can't see why these have an issue
with that,
but they changed the rules that often.
It's always a double check.
And I think because these do update the site quite a lot.
Well, I've definitely seen that before.
Yeah.
And to be honest, you can still tick water sports as something that you enjoy
on your profile.
So if they're still allowing that on there, I think it's fine.
The rules more change for the free, the free photos and stuff like that.
But everything that goes on in the chat rooms and in the private gallery and
stuff like that.
That's still all okay.
Still all the same rules apply.
Yeah.
But yeah, like Chloe said, no, like no toys, no photos in the background.
Of course, no people make sure all your photos and videos.
It's just you unless you get consent and stuff like that.
So yeah, just bear all that in mind.
Yeah.
Was that all or was anything else?
No, I just wanted to know about that.
Yeah.
Okay.
Cool.
So something else you can add to your profile is blogs.
So, you know, if you like writing and you couldn't write a few blogs on there,
you can write about your normal every day or you can write more like fantasy
style blogs and stuff like that, whatever, whatever inspires you to write, you
can write that on your profile.
Again, it's just more things to book your profile out for the clients to look
through.
Right.
You can, you know, when I go to New Zealand, my partner there.
He's up for doing some cam work with me.
How long does it take to get his profile on or to make us a lovely profile?
Yeah, you just have to make a duo.
So you definitely can't come on yours.
Or if he had his own one, you couldn't do that together.
You got to do a duo.
And to be honest, it can be done quite fast.
If you start on the first day, you arrive.
If you just, well, you could even start in the days before you can ask.
You can ask him to send him some photos of himself.
You've got some photos of yourself.
And we can make the profile and then the day you arrive or, you know, whenever
you feel up to it, like a suit towards the start of the trip, you can get it
verified.
And that takes up to 48 hours, if done correctly, if everything's done
correctly from the.
So it can take just a couple of days. That's the ideal scenario.
I just made a profile for one of our members last week and it got verified like
that within 24 hours.
It was done.
So it can be done very fast.
But if anything's done incorrectly and they have to then ask for favour
documentation that delays the process.
But we can tell you exactly what you need to do for it to be done correctly.
So then hopefully that won't happen.
So it can just take a few minutes.
Yeah.
Okay, that's brilliant.
Okay, perfect.
So yeah, just let us know.
And we'll make sure we keep on top of that one.
So if you can make the most of it.
And then we zap for it.
So you know.
Yeah, why not?
I love coming with my partner.
It's so much easier and more fun and easier because, you know, you have a last.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
All right, then.
Brilliant.
Okay.
Perfect.
Okay, then, so something else that you could add to your profile is an
introduction video.
So you could add it for free, maybe in your videos and it can just doesn't need
to be anything explicit.
Of course, it can just be you introducing yourself or just even a video of you
smiling and waving.
I don't know.
It could be just something quick.
Just so they can see you and, you know, be more intrigued to see more of you
and get to know you more.
So that's something you could possibly add to your profile.
Mm.
Um, something else you can add is you can write in your bio to let the clients
know when you'll be online.
I remember one of our really successful members used to do this.
She would always write.
I'm going to I'm online, you know, Monday to Friday, 11 p.m. Till 1 a.m.
And she set a schedule and that's all she'd done.
And she would always be so busy in those hours because all her clients would go
to her profile and say,
Oh, yeah, if I want to come with her, these are times I've got I can come with
her.
So then they would they would come and they would come and come in in those
times.
Um, so if you're someone who knows what your schedule is, it is worth writing
on your profile.
You know, Saturday, I'm going to be online.
Ten till two, Sunday, I'll be online for till seven or whatever it is.
I don't know.
You can write it on your profile.
But if you're someone who doesn't really know, you know, if you just go online
randomly, you don't have to do that.
Of course, but yeah, that's an option.
And I ask another question.
Sure.
Um, when we do come in for as a couple, um, obviously, if we're going to put a
show on.
Do you put a time of when the show is going to be happening and how long it
will be?
And do you put the rates up for that?
Um, you can actually do this.
Yes.
You can create like a, like a show and like, you know, advertise it and say, on
this day, we're going to do the same show, like whatever it is, what type of
show it's going to be.
So you can do that.
So then, you know, clients will see if we're off the weekend and they'll be
like, oh, yeah, the show is going to be on on the weekends.
I'm going to make sure I go to that.
So yeah, you can do that.
And what would you charge roughly for a couple per minute.
And per minute, you can charge a little bit more than your.
What I would do.
A five credits a minute.
Um, five, you could do cards for sure.
But what I would do is actually, if I were you, I would just look at the
couples that are online.
Take a look at the average.
The average price and charge, charge around that, because, you know, if you
charge too high, then they might be like, oh, you know, there's over couples
online that charge a little bit less.
So if you charge too low, that's the point you may as well, at least find the
middle ground. That's what I do.
Whenever I'm online, and I'm not, maybe I'm not as busy in that moment to think
, Oh, maybe I should have a look at my prices.
And then I'll look and I'll see all my prices are way too high at the moment.
You know, consecutive regarding who else is online at that time. So now I'll
lower my prices by like 10, say to point, like 10 or 20 people a minute.
And then I'll see all those coming in. So I think concept, like, set in a
competitive rate, definitely helps.
And also whatever you're comfortable with, if you know you're going to be doing
, you know, like a sex show, for example, you know, then you only want, you only
want to sit and read, pay a minute for that, then charge that, even if it's
high, then charge whatever you feel comfortable to.
But if you're happy to just charge, you know, the average, then that's probably
going to do well in your favour because then the clients are seeing, Oh, yeah,
they're not charging much higher than everybody else.
So then you're more likely to have a larger group of clients come up with you.
Yeah.
But there's not that many couples online, to be honest, there's way more solo.
Especially young, especially oldies.
Yeah, there's, there's not many at all. So you should, you should do very well
because there's loads of like girls that can, but the couple profiles, you'll
see there might be a handful online at one time.
Whereas for the girls, there's over just hundreds online sometimes at a time.
So there's a lot less. So, so yeah.
Yeah, good luck with that. Let us know how you go with that one.
Oh, well, he's quite excited about it.
Oh, there he is. Okay, then. So something else regarding the profile is make
sure you've got an intriguing and eye-catching bio.
So as you can see, Chloe's here. She's got different tabs. So, you know, you
can go into different parts of your personality or cam persona through the tabs
.
And she's also got some bits in bold, you know, you can even put emojis and
stuff like that. So yeah, spend some time working on your profile because they
do read it, not everyone, but a lot of clients will read it because they'll say
to you, Oh, I read your profile and I really like this bit or, you know,
whatever else.
So it is worth doing that. Can you put in your profile as well that you do
actually have a couple's profile as well to look and give them details of that.
Can you do that?
Yeah, you can. You can actually link your profile to another one.
So we can show you how to do this, but yeah, at the bottom of your profile, it
will say, I think it just says links with or in collaboration, I don't have
something like basically saying that your profile is linked to another.
And then they literally just click right into your joint profile there. You
could potentially write about it in the bio, what I done is when me and my
partner made our joint profile.
I had one a while ago, but then we didn't use it so we ended up making a new
one a couple of weeks ago. I basically just told all my regulars, I emailed
them. And I said, just to let you know, I'm now operating on a duo profile as
well.
And, you know, give them like a little bit of like, wrote a few things that
would excite them. And then, you know, like we're doing a live show at some
sort of time, if you'd like to join us or something yeah.
Yeah, for sure. So yeah, you can definitely let your clients know about that.
Okay, there's something else you can add to your profile is FAQs so you can at
the bottom, if I was to scroll down here, obviously this is just a screenshot
so I can't show you on this bit.
But at the bottom of your profile have all the FAQs so, you know, maybe, maybe
you'll keep getting asked something that you don't want to be asked anymore.
For example, maybe the clients keep asking to meet you so you could write on
your FAQs, you can write off the question, do you do meet and then you answer
yourself.
So you could say, I don't do meet, please don't ask me about this in the chat
room or something like that.
So, you know, you can have anything in your FAQs, but that's just an example.
So another thing you can do to bulk out your profile is complete the AdultWork
interview.
This literally can be very simple, doesn't take that long, and it's just here
on the interview tab so the clients can get to know you a little bit more.
Of course, you don't have to answer these questions, you know, truthfully, and
you can answer them as your webcam persona if you want to, or you can answer
them completely truthfully, whatever you prefer.
So I think else to consider for the profile is that you can edit your webcam
price and tagline or category.
So, as I mentioned just before, this is something that I do, if I'm online and
I'm not that busy, I'll think, oh, you know what, I'll just lower my price a
little bit.
Or if I'm really busy or if I've got, if I know, sit and clients are coming to
come with me, maybe I'll bump it up just a little bit more because I know they
're my regular client, they come to me regardless, you know, I wouldn't put it
from two credits to five credits because they're going to know that.
But I might put it from 2.5 to 2.7, might just put it up just where do you
change that please.
You change that in your webcam and webcam settings, so before when I showed on
the menu, when I logged in myself to come and I showed on the top right hand
corner, you click settings.
And then on your free mode, you can change your price per minute, I went
through it all before on the webcam screen, that's where you do it.
All right.
Yeah, so you do all that there and you can also edit your tagline.
So your tagline is what your client will see when they scroll over your profile
or hover over it on the main page.
So you can change your tagline every time you could say, I'm wearing my brand
new underwear set today, come tell me what you think, or, you know, I'm feeling
really naughty today.
Or whatever it is, you can write something on your tagline just to intrigue the
clients to come come with you.
Where's the tagline?
You do that on the webcam settings as well.
So you go into my details as a profile, webcam settings and then in there,
something got popular.
Yeah, thanks.
Yeah.
But if you ever have any issues, just let us know and we'll show you exactly
where to find all this.
But it's all done in the settings.
All right.
Okay, then.
Oh, there was one more thing there, what was that?
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Finally, you can link your social media.
You can link your Twitter.
So if anyone has a Twitter for their campus owner, you can also link it to your
profile.
And I think most of us don't have that, but I just put that in there just in
case anyone did.
Okay, then.
So now let's take a little look at phone calls, SMS and direct IM.
All of these photos on this PowerPoint or most of them on this PowerPoint stay
off on my recent shoots.
A lovely lot of looking really amazing there on the phone.
Okay.
So not feeling to get ready for webcam, but still want to earn some money.
Try phone calls, SMS or direct IM to bump up your earnings.
Okay, so phone calls and SMS chat.
So what you'll need to do is you'll need to turn it on on the registration
details, like I showed you earlier.
So you just tick the box and then you'll need to verify your phone number and
as it works.
And just so you know, the clients will never receive your number.
So it's completely safe.
So although.
Oh, yeah.
So although the texts are coming through to your number, they don't see it.
They see a different one and then it gets sent to you.
So yeah, I didn't answer them because I thought they would get my nap.
Yeah, no, no, they definitely won't see it.
So that's good that you can still keep in contact with them without actually
giving away your personal information.
All right.
So yeah, this is a great way to keep in touch with regular clients and to let
them know when you're going to be online.
So, you know, if you're not feeling to come one day or you can't, maybe you've
got people around or, you know, you're not feeling too good or whatever it is.
You can still connect with your regular clients.
Obviously make money and then let them know when you're going to be online.
So you can be chatting with them on text on the phone.
And then you can be like, Oh, I'm actually going to be online later on today at
six p.m. Shall we, shall we catch up?
So that way you're being obviously making money with all of the texts.
And then you're lining up even more, you know, even more than calls through
this.
So I think this is a good thing to use.
And the credit's spelled up fast with little effort required.
So obviously we're on our phones a lot, right?
So it's just quite probably easy just to text them back.
And I'm pretty sure that it's pure text, not that yet, not the text size.
So if you, you know, if you want to send them a message, you can maybe say a
few things on the first text and then send another one with a few more
sentences in rather than sending it as one text.
That way you're making money for both rather than just sending it as one.
Okay.
So we get not doing not get charged for sending a text.
Um, I think it depends on your phone provider is Chloe.
Oh, no, it's Sophie on the call today.
Sophie there.
She knows more about this. Exactly. I'm not sure.
Hey, so, yeah, no, I'm here. Don't worry. I'm listening away. I was in the bus
with a little girl. So that's why I was muted and that had face, but I've just
got out.
So if someone texted you, you send a text back.
We get charged, don't leave for that. I think it depends on your network
provider.
Like Georgia said, so I get free text as part of my call plan.
I've got to see myself look like a double you don't charge us. No.
No, we get paid for every time we send back. So if a client, you add all work
charges them for the initial text that they send to you for every text that you
send back, you get nearly one credit. It's like 0.99.
Oh, my credits. So that's why Jesus saying send little and often messages.
And then just be aware, when you were abroad, I was in Thailand the other week,
and my network provider was sent was charging me 30 pence per text. I was
sending.
They were really good client texting me all day. And it was worth spending the
30 p and I was still getting, you know, about 50 p back. So I was making about
20 people text, but then he was coming to see me on common stuff as well.
Yeah. So it is worth it. Definitely the text. A lot of them will say, I'll just
see your profile when you're next online.
Or it's just really subtle texting, isn't it? Like, again, like you said,
everyone's on the phone a lot. Nobody's going to bat an eyelid. You're like
that on your phone, but you're actually going, oh, yeah, one cure.
You know, me, nobody knows.
So it is sent through to me and some of them were explicit and I thought, Oh,
my God, I'm not answering to them because they'll get my number.
No, no, it goes through a server. So there's like a middleman. So you text the
server.
And then they text that server and it like, you know, you don't, they don't see
your number. If you pick on your phone call settings. If you take the top box,
say in pre booked phone chat, or disable free book phone chat.
Keep that ticked because otherwise they may get your number, the pre booked one
.
They will book a call with you, and you get attacked day in so and so it was
booked a call and ring them at this time. So you accept that and then ring them
.
So you disable that disable.
Yeah, tick the top box.
Okay, we can do a video call later if you want. Okay, you know, we've done
before, haven't we. You're always out at all, not at all. You just learn and
pick my brains later if you want to honestly message me with anything.
I'm not that old and I'm not tech savvy at all. I've had to learn this stuff
just doing.
I've learned the bare minimum and I just about get through.
Well, we'll talk about it. I don't worry.
Don't worry.
Thank you so if there anything else you could add regarding phone calls and SMS
.
I know there's another thing, the certain things you can't talk. Do they listen
to them.
They can do. It's not. They don't listen to every single call or monitor every
single text or monitor every single adult.
But I think they have like a certain words get flagged up.
And most of the time now people ask me stuff.
And I'll just go. No, sorry. Not into that.
If you wanted to be very, very subtle.
You can be by putting spaces between the words and just using them.
What about live chat though.
Do they listen to the live chat?
Because they're not necessarily always listening, but they could.
They do have the option to monitor phone calls and stuff, apparently.
And then could I get a lot of like, mummy with some, you know, that kind of
thing or.
Just say, Oh, I'm your step mummy, wink, wink.
Let's use our imaginations, wink, wink. That's what I do.
I get a lot of stuff and I'm like, no, no step, family, la, la, la.
Yeah, it's common sense. Anything illegal is illegal.
You know, kid, animals, incest, all that is totally illegal.
Total, no, no.
So I wasn't just to protect yourself.
Because no, no clients on there is worth getting your profiles deleted over.
They're not the right clients for you. Just say, no, thanks mate.
Move on and you'll find better quality.
Don't make you feel sick.
Yeah, true. It's not worth it. It's not worth risking it.
Just for that one phone call, that one text or that one cam session.
Yeah, you know, even if that cam session's going for a long time and you're
making good money on it,
it's still not worth to risk the future of your whole profile.
I am just, you know, by breaking the rules.
Because they are a lot trick to these days. They never used to be the strict.
I used to get it away with murder. I'm not going to lie, but not anymore.
It's not worth it at all.
Yeah.
This is my time to be a lot more naughty.
And now it's, I've had my profile completely deleted before and locally problem
with these.
You're not a scam. You're not a scam.
Today I've learned my ways. I've learned my lesson.
I won't do it again.
If you say so.
Okay then.
Let's move on to direct I am. So direct I am.
It's for anyone who doesn't know, it's basically just like a live chat, but
without the webcam.
So you log in just like you was on webcam, but they can't see you.
You can't see them. You're just typing away.
And so you switch it on on the webcam set and page.
And when you do, remember to lower your price per minute.
Because the clients do pay less for direct I am then on webcam, which is fair
enough.
Makes sense. Obviously if they can see you as well, it's an extra thing.
So they should be paying that bit more.
But if it's just typing back and forth, you do have to lower your prices a
little bit.
And just to get people into your room.
And so the good thing about direct I am is, is that you can do it from anywhere
.
You know, you could be on the train. You could be, you know, have someone in
front of you and they won't even know what you were doing.
You can do it obviously without having your head or makeup or outfit on or
whatever else.
It's easy just to throw on and just make a few extra credits while launching
around.
I know that some of our members actually have really good success on this.
Like I said, on those days where they don't really feel like getting ready to
go online on webcam.
They'll turn on their direct I am. You can just have it logged on while you're
partnering around the house or whatever.
But you could actually end up doing really well and, you know, even making like
really good money on direct I am.
So yeah, it's worth putting it on on those days that you don't want to come.
Any questions with that one? I'll show them move on to the next slides.
No, that's okay.
Okay, cool.
Okay, then.
So now I'll go through how to get more clients into your chat room.
Again, a lovely photo from our recent shoot.
Okay, so there are some things you can do to drive more clients to your chat
room.
We recommend trying at least a few of these points listed below as it can make
a huge difference as to how busy you are,
which in turn means you're making more money.
Okay, so the first thing is bidding to be on the front page.
It can really help.
Now this is something I do every time I go online.
I always speak about this.
As I showed before on the campaign, you press boost.
So it used to be called bidding, but now it's boost, but it's the same thing.
You press boost and then you put in a couple of credits free.
Start off with free credits.
If it goes yellow or orange, it means you're definitely not going to be on the
front page.
So there's no point.
So then you put in four credits and then it might have went green.
If it goes green, it means you're going to be on the front page.
So always just flick between the amount of credits is to see how many you're
going to need.
In busy periods, you will pay five, six, maybe even more credits an hour to be
on the front page, whereas in the quieter times they charge a bit less.
Obviously, if you're putting in, you know, five credits to be online for the
front page and you've done that for one hour and you didn't really do well and
then another hour and you don't do well,
I wouldn't recommend then spending again another five credits, maybe just put
your losses on that one and try again the next day or later on that day or
whenever it is your next go online.
But with that being said, it is rare to be on the front page and not make the
credits back at least that you paid to be on there.
Never mind, you know, make more and you do normally do well by being on the
front page and that's why we suggest bidding.
Now, if you want to be on the front page, but you don't want to pay or maybe
you don't actually have any credits in your account at the moment, like I've
just noticed I don't have any amount and I'm going to come after this.
What I would do then is I would go on free chat.
Now, this is something that in the past, you'd never would have hated me saying
this for myself because I used to really not enjoy free chat, but it actually
got better free chat now because you can see if the clients have got credit to
enter in your free chat.
So, and people can even tip you in free chat and stuff like that.
So, yeah, my thoughts have changed a lot on free chat.
I actually really love it now and I think it's a great tool.
And it was actually through the success of our members on free chat, which made
me realise, actually, this is a good thing.
Maybe I should try it more.
And so, yeah, so free chat, obviously, it's quite self-explanatory.
It's free.
You're not getting paid to be in there.
So, you can set your duration of how long people can view for free fall without
before they get kicked out.
I have mine set to just five minutes.
So, clients can come in there for five minutes.
If they don't take me to a paid chat, it kicks them out.
You can set it for five, 10, 15, 20.
You can set it for as long as you want.
What about one minute?
No, no, I wish.
The lowest is five, which isn't so bad.
It actually is over quite fast.
So, yeah, just five minutes is the lowest.
But then you can set within what time period.
So, they can view you for five minutes per hour.
For example, you can set it as that.
So, every hour, it resets.
Or every two hours, every three hours, every 24.
It's entirely up to you how you set that.
We recommend, of course, not letting them in there for too long for free
because you want to get paid on the end of the day.
But, free chat is actually a really good feature because it puts you a lot of
the time on the front page.
And even if you're not on the front page, you will get more traffic to your
chat because it's free.
Obviously, more people are joining.
So, if you're ever quiet and you don't want to pay for the front page or don't
have credit to,
or even if you just want to try it out, I'd definitely recommend trying free
chat.
Obviously, in there, you don't want to do much, you don't want to show much.
You want to be smiling and inviting and engaging with the clients, but you don
't want to give too much away.
Of course, if they start asking you things that you would normally do in group
or private, just say,
"Just take me to group or take me to private." We can do that in there.
But, yeah, a lot of the time, the clients are using free chat.
Just to pop in, to view you quickly before they take you to a paid chat.
And if you are going to use it, bear in mind that you don't answer calls in
free chat, they just enter.
So, as soon as you press start, as soon as you press login to go live, be ready
for people to enter your call.
Whereas, when you're not on free chat, as we know, no one can see you until you
press accept on a call.
On free chat, they just enter and leave as they wish you don't accept them in,
so you just have to be ready for that one.
Personally, I turn on free chat. I'll sit in front of the laptop for 10, 15
minutes, if that.
And if I still haven't been taken to a free and paid chat, I turn it off.
I don't spend too long in there, because if it did, I think I'd start to hate
it.
I just do it in small doses, so it doesn't feel too overwhelming.
But, hopefully, you know, every time you go on free chat, or most times at
least, you'll get taken to a paid chat, so it's totally worth it.
Okay, so something else you can do to get more clients in your chat room is
email old regular clients to tell them that you've been, that you're returning
back to come after some time off.
So, if you've not been online for a while, and, you know, it's a bit slow,
because you need to build it back up again, you can just go on to your emails
and just email all your clients in there, the same thing.
So, I have to run for each one. How do you do them all at once, because it piss
es me off, I've got 37 now.
Yeah, sorry, it's not all at once. What I meant was you can just basically
email them roughly the same things you can, you've got to do it one by one.
Yeah, it's not all right. Sorry, that would be, that would be a good feature.
That would be easy if you could do that, but you just have to click into each
one.
If you just have a copy and paste, you could just paste it in and just, that
could say, "Hey, how have you been?"
I'm back online after some time away, so excited to be back and I'm online now
with you around, or something like that, I don't know.
And it just, just opens up the communication again and hopefully, hopefully at
least once they send 30 emails, hopefully at least one of those are online at
that same time and they come to come with you.
With this, every time I go back online, you can set special offers for
specifically, set special offers for specific clients.
So, again, this is for a lot of the time, clients who have sent fetishes, they
might want to see you do a same thing, for example, water sports, as we were
talking about earlier.
You can set a special offer to say, you know, however long it's going to be, so
half an hour call for this amount of credits, and it's going to be a call on
water sports, and then your clients can pay for that special offer.
And then you have to obviously then do the call around that.
Another thing you can do is make a social media account for your camp persona
and direct clients to your AdultWork that way.
And I know that a lot of people don't like to do this because they like to be
discreet, but if this is something that, you know, you're happy to try, then it
's worth it.
You can make a Twitter or even an Instagram and, you know, you don't even have
to put your face on there, you can make it completely anonymous and then build
up your following on that and then tell that following.
I'm going to be online at these hours or I've just logged on to come and then
link your ads or work that way.
So that's some things you can do to get clients into your chat room.
Okay, I think we've just got one or two slides left now, so I will go through
my top tips.
So probably if you've been on calls before, you might have hear me saying these
before, but to be honest, they don't really change.
I keep with the same fundamentals and I feel as though that works like, you
know, if you nail the fundamentals, you don't need to be always coming up with
new ideas and new ways is that obviously that's good too.
But there are some core things that you can that you can do, which normally
work.
Okay, so your webcam set up so this is a big one so you want to make sure that
your camera is clear that you have good lighting and that the space around you
is open and inviting and nice and clear.
And because you're at the end of the day, they're paying to see you so they
want to actually be able to see you properly.
So I think nailing your webcam set up is quite important.
I have this light here that I use, I've shown this before many times on the
call.
As you can see, this is not when I come, I do a few different things with the
with the thing, but as you can see today, you can you can see me but not so
well.
But then when you put the light, it just changes everything and you can see me
so clearly.
So I got this from Amazon, it was super cheap.
It's got different settings and I really recommend this obviously it's very
portable, you could take it on holiday if you were to come here like stuff like
that.
And I just put that a ring light.
Is that what they call a ring light?
That's not a ring light. I do have a ring light here I'll show you.
This is just like a handheld light can even be put on your phone to have a
selfie light.
So you can put it like that to like obviously, you know, take photos of
yourself or videos or come even from your phone.
Or you can just click on the back of your laptop.
Yeah.
So that's just, I think it's just called a portable light that wants to be
honest, but a ring light.
Looks like this, obviously it's not on at the moment, but it's like a big stand
.
And yeah, so that would be put it behind your laptop, so that's a ring light.
I do recommend both, like they're both good.
But to be honest for me for travelling this past couple of years, this has been
my best friend because I've just been able to take it everywhere with me.
And now that I've settled somewhere, I've bought myself a ring light as well.
Good to have, you know, good to have both why not.
But if I would choose one, I would choose the small one.
So yeah, I definitely recommend that.
Okay, so competitive rate for price per minute, I've already spoke about this,
so I don't need to speak about that again, but that's definitely one of my top
tips.
So your profile picture.
So this is like the main thing that the clients are seeing before they come
with you.
Sometimes they click into your profile and look at everything else.
Sometimes they don't.
So the profile picture is one of the main things that you'll need to nail.
And you want something that's quite, that you're taking up quite a lot of the
photo in.
You don't want to be too far away to where they can't see you.
And something you can do actually as well.
You can put like a border around your photo.
And I've seen some of our members doing this.
So you could do like a red border, for example, just a thin border, but it just
makes it more eye-catching.
And it makes you a little bit different to everybody else on there.
So that's something that some of our members do.
If you're maybe thinking, you know, you've got a few photos in mind and you don
't know which one to use.
You can ask goes for our guidance or you can try trial different ones.
Sometimes I'll have a profile picture on and I'll think it's great.
I'll love the photo, but then it doesn't really work so well.
And then I'll put a different one on that, you know, I think is okay, but it's
not my favourite.
But then that seems to get so many calls and get a lot of attention to my
profile.
So it's good just trial and different ones and see what works best.
And, you know, when I go away, he is a photographer actually.
So I'm going to get a load of pictures done.
Oh, perfect.
So I just send them through to my mentor, don't I? And then she'll put them on
for me.
Yeah, you can do that. You can upload them yourself.
But if you don't know how to do it and need help, that's also fine.
We can upload your mentor and do that. But yeah, that's handy.
That he's going to take some photos of you as well.
Yeah.
There's a lot going on in big weeks.
Why not? Have you been there before to New Zealand?
Oh, that'll be fun.
Well, if it works out all right, I'll be emigrating there.
Oh, yeah, nice.
Change of scenery.
Okay, so another one of my top tips is bid, bid, bid.
So to bid to be on the front page.
As I said before, I've done this like for the past 11 years.
Every time I go online, I always bid.
And if I don't have money in the beginning, like I said, I'll do free chat to
get clients in.
Get them into a paid chat, get a couple of credits in my account.
And then for the next hour, I'll definitely bid to put myself on the front.
Not everyone uses this.
We still have members who have really good success without using the bid mode
and like the boost mode.
Sorry.
So, you know, it's up to you, but this is one of my top tips.
This is what I recommend.
Okay.
So something else I would say is that consistency is key.
So like anything, the more you put in, the more consistent you are, you know,
the more you're going to get out of it.
And it does really ring true with webcam.
And I noticed myself when I've not been online consistently for a while, it
takes a bit of time for me to then get busy again.
But if I'm going on consistently, even if it's for, you know, two hours, like
if I'm only going on for like two hour sessions, you know, not going on for so
long.
Even if I go on two hours every other day, it's better to do that.
For me, anyway, and then to do like an eight hour shift once every two weeks,
you know, it's better to do little often stay consistent.
Then your profile keeps coming up on the front page or on the, you know, that
you're online and you just keep getting seen more and more and more.
So yeah.
I think as I think that sometimes we can get overwhelmed thinking about going
online and thinking, Oh, you know, I've got to spend hours online.
I've got to do this, this and that just logging on and just spending an hour or
two, you know, every couple of days at least really does go a long way.
That's if you're able to, of course, if your schedule allows for it.
Okay, so I'm still listening nice to get ready. That's fine. You do whatever
you need. Okay.
This is going to be on the website anyway, so anything that's missed, you can
always, you can always watch it back.
Okay. So another one of my top tips is to do the admin work around calm.
So client emails, as I've mentioned, sending flats and updating your profile.
So I've already went into two of those things, but the sending flats. This is
something you can do.
But you send it to new clients. So it's actually a good way to connect with new
clients.
So you send them like a flare does they call it. So you send them like a wink
or a kiss or something like that.
It's basically just making contact with them, making connection with them.
It's good to do this when you just sat waiting for calls. You may as well be
spending that time to try and get more clients into your chat.
Content, that's another one of my tips. Obviously, we spoke about this already
today. So just being on top of their putting new photos on their new videos,
making sure the content you've already got your happy with.
Or something I actually done, which I didn't even realise there's always good
going through your photos, just to make sure that nothing slipped in there that
didn't mean to.
I actually was going through my private gallery a few weeks ago, and I was mort
ified. There were two photos in there that I should not have ever gotten into
there.
I don't know how they got in there, but they did. And they were in there for
quite a while before I noticed possibly an over a year.
So yeah, maybe going through your content as well, just to make sure that
everything in there is what you actually want to be in there is definitely
important.
Yeah, I was so mortified when I seen that these sent photos have been uploaded.
I was like, "Oh my God, how did they end up in there?" So yeah, probably best
that I always check.
And finally, my final top tip, which actually is a very important one, is
making a note of clients using names of points about them.
So if you want to get regular clients, it's all about connection, it's all
about them feeling as though they're seen, they're heard, they're understood.
So if you've got loads of clients coming through your chat room all the time,
how are you supposed to remember exactly what that client is into or what they
told you?
Or how are you supposed to remember that? You can't. Maybe you could. If you're
here and there, you're not going to remember everything about everyone.
So what I do is, I just have a note tab on my laptop, and in the notes, I just
have the username of each client, and then a few points about them.
So it could be in our call, we don't SPH, but he's not into cock and ball
torture, for example.
Like that would probably be something about one of my sub clients. So then you
know when they next come back, you can do SPH with them, but then stick clear
of the things they don't like.
And even stuff like, you know, stuff about them, maybe they've told you, "Oh, I
've just got a promotion at work."
Then you could say, "Oh, I've just got a new job or whatever." You could say, "
Oh, how's your new job going?"
But the next time you chat, and they'll think, "Oh my God, do you remember that
I told that I got a new job?"
You know, it is, you didn't actually remember you just wrote it in the notes.
So trust me, this goes a long way with regular clients, and regular clients are
where you make your money.
You'll still get new clients passing through that will spend on you, but those
returning clients, that's what you want because that's where you know that you
're guaranteed to make good money because you've got these regulars coming all
the time.
So yeah, making notes about them and making it seem like you've remembered all
of the points about them really, really does help.
And on the flip side of that, not remembering them, and you know, them thinking
that, "Oh, they're just another client of yours that you don't even care about.
That can go against you."
Because then they can think, "Why would I even bother coming with this woman? I
'm spending hundreds on here every week and she can't even remember what I'm in
too. She can't even remember what type of stuff I like on Cam or this or that."
Which is fair enough, they'll probably end up going elsewhere. So yeah, just
making a note of your clients with some points about them really, really does
help if I choose one of my top tips, like one of my most important ones, that
will definitely be it.
So yeah, that's that. I think we have one final slide. So being productive
while waiting for calls.
Okay, so instead of just sitting around and waiting for someone to call you,
there are things you can do while you wait, which could make a big difference
to how busy you are.
Okay, so email and everyone to tell them you're online. So this is not just for
when you've like, you know, written back after weeks. You could have been
online yesterday, but you can still today message them and say, "Hey, I'm
online. Are you around?" You know, something simple.
It might take you five or ten minutes to sit there and email everyone, but you
're just sitting waiting for calls anyway, and those five or ten minutes, you
know, that could mean that a few of those clients see that and then come to Cam
you and obviously that's what you want.
So you can leave feedback for all your past calls. I do this all the time as
well. I think it's great because it just puts your profile out there more on
the site and also your client will see that you've left them feedback and one,
they're going to be happy about that.
And two, they'll think, "Oh yeah, she was great. I want to come with it again."
So it just, it just, you know, it just allows your client just to be reminded
of you again.
Take pictures and videos for your profile. So, you know, while you're all done
ready for Cam, you may as well spend that time to take some new photos if you
need some.
You can try Free Chart. Obviously, we spoke about this. So yeah, if you just
start around and it's not busy, then, you know, why not just 10 on Free Chart?
Yeah, you're not paid for those five, 10, 15 minutes that you spend in there,
but it can be worth it because then you can get paid calls from it.
So get ready to bid for the next hour. So now you do actually get notified in
your chat box. It'll tell you the next hour is coming up.
Do you want to boost to be on the front page? But let's say you've walked away
from your laptop and you don't see this.
What I always do is even still now, I'll just set alarms on my phone. So I'll
set an alarm for five minutes to the next hour.
So if it was for now, I'll be setting it for five to one. And then, whether I'm
at my laptop and I see it or I'm away, at least my phone will let me to come
back and bid.
You know, maybe you'll think, oh, I won't forget. You know, I'll just do it at
five to the hour. But maybe you would forget and then it locks out and you've
missed that whole hour.
So it's always good just to get ready for that, whether that means setting
alarms or just, you know, making sure you're ready, whatever, however that
looks for you.
Okay, so you can also take a look at the client's connection page message,
message potential clients and send flights. So we spoke about that as well.
Update your profile or tagline. So all of the stuff that we said earlier about
updating the profile, you know, instead of using your time outside of come to
do this, you could, you can use that time, obviously, as well, when you're not
live streaming.
But when you're live streaming and you're just that way of a cause, you can
also be updating your profile in that time as well.
You can do our training. So, yeah, you can log on to the members area and take
a little look through that. See if there's some training in there that you
haven't done.
You can do that while you're waiting for calls.
And also, you know, maybe you don't want to do any webcam stuff. You just want
to do something else. You can just sit there, read the book, or just complete
any outstanding tasks.
So maybe you've just got some, you know, life admin stuff to do online. You can
just do that while you're waiting for calls.
I feel as though it's always good to just keep yourself busy when you're
waiting for calls. I mean, it's up to the individual. Some people might like to
just sit back and not do anything.
But for me, I like to be active while waiting for calls. Otherwise, I can get
kind of bored and not motivated to continue. If I'm just sat for a while
waiting and waiting and waiting.
If at least if I'm doing something, it's not like I'm just sat around wasting
time. If that makes sense.
So, yeah, I think that's it for today's call.
Does anybody have any questions or anything that they would like to add?
No, I'll be on this afternoon. I've got to take a dementia guy out and then I
'll come back and get online.
Oh, yeah. Okay, nice. Well, let us know how you go. I'm good luck with that.
Well, that's my job. I'm a carer on I am between.
Oh, yeah, sorry. I meant that I made good luck with going online, but yeah,
also enjoy it.
Yeah, nice.
Elle says, "Great to see you, Kay."
Oh, hi, Elle.
She doesn't have a camera at the moment, but she is here.
Yeah, I haven't been on for a while, so I will get on. It's funny because when
I get on, they all go, "Where have you been? Where have you been?"
That's nice. They're still there, like, waiting, you know, like, and they've
noticed that you've gone, so it shows that you must be in high demands, Kay.
If they're noticing that I'm waiting for you.
Okay, then, well, thank you everyone for coming.
I will upload this to the members area, so if there are any parts that you know
you'd like to go over again or that you missed, you can't watch it back.
But, yeah, good luck to anyone going online today. I'm going to be going online
myself.
So, yeah, let me know if you're online and we'll check in with each other and
see how we're doing.
But, yeah, so lovely to see you all, and thank you for coming.
Bye. Thank you.
No worries.
Okay.
Thank you.
That was me.
Bye.
Thank you.
That was amazing.
Bye!